-= CHD字幕组 =-
校订翻译：dxch dahongying
你以为你一天的工作很糟糕吗？
You think you've had a bad day at work?
我觉得我比你惨
I think I got you beat.
这不是我
That's not me.
不 这是我的搭档
Nope, that's my partner.
去你的！
Suck it!
我在这儿
There I am.
三四天前
Three or four days ago,
我不知道有这个世界的存在
I didn't know this world existed.
但三四天前
But three or four days ago,
我还不是冥界警局的一份子
I wasn't in the Rest In Peace Department.
片名：冥界警局
三、四天前…
一里之外我就听到你过来了
I heard you coming a mile away.
奇怪 法国女孩都该骑在波士顿最棒的男人身上
Look at this, French girl gets the drop on Boston's finest.
你却骑在我身上啊 对吗？
You got the drop on me, huh?
我现在感觉自己像个天才
But I feel like a genius right now.
如果您打算要更好的
I couldn't have planned this better.
好吧 天才 有棵桔树倒在后园里
Well, genius, there is an orange tree in the backyard.
怎么会如此？
How did that get there?
是的 后园里有颗桔树
Yeah, there is an orange tree in the backyard.
真奇怪
How weird.
我不知道它是怎么到这儿来的
I don't know how it got here.
我也不知道
Me neither.
你知道它象征繁荣吗？
You know it's a symbol of prosperity, don't you?
没有 我从来没听过
No, I've never heard that.
是真的 问问佛罗里达州的人们
It is, yeah. Ask anyone in Florida.
不 你疯了吗
No, you're crazy.
它可能无法活过冬天
This tree is never gonna make it through the winter.
可能有人无法活过冬天
We might not make it through the winter
因为这房子里很冷！
in this freezing little house!
但我就爱我们的冷房子
I love our freezing little house.
你也爱 对吗？
You do, do you?
是吗？
Yeah?
你别无所求了吗？
But don't you want more?
你总是担心钱不够
You're always worried about money.
你不是想要好房子吗？好车子吗？
Don't you want a real house? A car?
我才不担心钱 是你担心
I don't worry about money, you do.
我需要的一切都在这里
I have everything I need right here.
我的丈夫陪伴着我
My husband, with me.
你将会一直拥有的
Well, you'll always have that.
我得去上班了
I gotta go to work.
我会告诉你什么时候你可以上班
I'll tell you when you can go to work.
真的吗？
Really?
当心扭到脚 爱你 亲爱的
Watch that ankle. I love you, baby.
再见 我也爱你
Bye. Love you.
什么时候我照片和奖杯才会在陈列柜中
Got my picture in a trophy case, I see.
看看这个 可以永垂不朽了
Look at that. Already immortalized.
那需要天时地利 我还能说什么？
Right place, right time. What can I say?
- 嘿 鲍比  - 你好
- Hey, Bobby. - Hey.
墨菲！天啊 加件浴衣吧
Murph! Jesus, get a robe or something.
那围巾可支撑不了
You're asking too much of that towel.
- 早上好 伙计  - 早上好
- Morning, partner. - Morning.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
记得周一员工聚会上见
Love to have you at the union meeting Monday.
不 不！上帝啊 墨菲
No, no! Sweet Jesus, Murphy.
我会射爆那东西
I will shoot that thing.
真令人受不了
That's pretty devastating.
这可能令我对工作留下创伤
It's gonna be a while before I get that image out.
嘿 你那份怎么样了？
Hey, what did you do with yours?
- 我埋了  - 真的吗？
- I buried it. - Really?
没开玩笑？
I thought you were joking about that.
不会有更糟的主意了
But it's not the worse idea.
它是黄金 你却埋了它 对吧？
It's gold, you bury it. Right?
听着 鲍比
Listen, Bobby.
我要退出
I'm out.
退出？
You're out?
听着
Look.
这对你不会有任何影响
Nothing has to change for you.
做你想做的
You do whatever you want,
对于我 它已结束了
but I'm putting mine in evidence. It's done.
老弟 我说我会处理好
Nicky, I said I would move it for us.
我会搞定一切的
I'll take care of everything.
我不是说这些 鲍比
That's not what I'm talking about, Bobby.
我是说今早她已怀疑我有问题
I'm talking about the way she looked at me this morning,
我早估到
I knew.
听着 我们只是去那里打击毒品的
Look, we went in there to make a drug bust,
仅此而已
which we did.
我们没想到天上竟然掉黄金
We didn't expect this gold to fall into our laps.
我们又不是故意的 但它就这么发生了
We weren't looking for it, but it happened.
我看出来了 你是为了朱莉娅做的
The way I see it, you do it for Julia.
为了你们的未来 这很简单
For your future together. It's simple.
不 她很幸福 我不想拿她的幸福冒险
No, she's happy. I'm not gonna risk that.
对不起 伙计
I'm sorry, buddy.
你说得对
You're right.
但我讨厌你说得对
I hate it when you're right.
我们要是上交东西的话
We gotta turn the whole thing in.
买游艇就没希望了
There goes the speedboat.
听着
Look.
别担心 我不会出卖你的
You don't have to worry, I'm not wagging my finger at you.
你做你想做的
You do whatever you want to do.
不 这仍令我不安
No, it's bothering me, too.
那就让我们一起变成老穷鬼
So, let's grow old and poor together.
听着 发现加尔萨了 还得到个地址
Listen up, we got Garza. We got an address.
等等 发现加尔萨？你真的肯定是他吗？
Wait, you got Garza? You got actual eyes on him?
有线人供出了他所有的冰毒交易
An informant gave up his whole meth operation.
他就在那儿 他跑不掉了
He's there, we got him.
好吧 我们开工吧 伙计
Okay, we're in business, partner.
再为陈列柜再加些新照片了
Get another picture in the trophy case.
你知道我们等待加尔萨出错等了多久吗？
You know how long we've been waiting for Garza to slip up.
这家伙是个毒贩 警察杀手
This guy's a meth dealer, a cop killer.
有30多个手下
He's got 30 guys with him.
抓住他不容易
He's not gonna go easy.
现在 准备好了 听听激动人心的
Now, stand by for inspiring,
来自侦探鲍比・海耶斯的有启发性的训话
motivating words from Detective Bobby Hayes.
我们今天不要吃枪子 如何？
How about we don't get shot today?
很好的建议 你是一个好警察
That's great advice. You're a good cop.
侦探海耶斯的意见是我们都不要中弹
Detective Hayes advises we should avoid getting shot.
还有 所有人都应该戴上他的魔力手链
And also, everybody should put their charm bracelets on now.
嘿 那是我祖母的
Hey, that's my grandmother's
圣克里斯多夫手链啊 你个白痴
Saint Christopher medal, jackass.
真可爱
It's adorable.
我依赖它的保护
I wear it for protection.
它的保护？这个才能挡子弹
It's for protection? Well, this stops bullets.
你戴那个是约不到女孩子的
Yours stops you from getting dates.
上吧！
Let's go!
行动！上吧！去！
Move it! Move it! Let's go!
跟上我 我们会先进入
On my lead. Let's put them on their heels.
注意安全 好吗？
Be safe, will you?
开门 开门
Knock, knock.
警察！
Police officer!
把东西带走
Take the stuff out of here.
快打包！快打包！
Bag the stuff! Bag the stuff!
我看到加尔萨
I see Garza.
他在楼梯上！
He's on the catwalk!
该死的！他从南面窗口逃走了
Damn it! Garza's out the south window.
天啊！
Jesus!
- 这真危险啊  - 你干什么呢？
- That was close. - What the hell are you doing?
你差点打到我了
You almost got me.
但是
But,
我不会让你上交黄金
I can't let you turn that gold in.
什么？
What?
“我的丈夫陪伴着我”
My husband, with me.
监察员
艰难的一天
Tough day.
这是正常的 起初是会有点吃惊的
It's normal to be a little tongue-tied at first.
我想让你明白我是来帮你的
I want you to know that I'm here to help you.
我也坐过那把椅子
I've sat in that chair.
所以放松点
So take your time.
慢慢来了解吧
Ease into it.
我要了解什么？
Ease into what?
来吧 天才 我知道你能行
Come on, genius. I know you can get there.
这是一个笑话吗？
This is a joke.
很滑稽
Hilarious.
我死了吗？
I'm dead?
说实话 当一个黑警察
Let's be honest, being a dirty cop
是一个被当面射杀的比例较高的职业
is one of the higher shot-in-the-face-percentage jobs.
我不是黑警察
That's not who I am.
真的吗 帅哥？
Really, pretty boy?
当你朝着审判之路行进时感觉如何？
How did it feel as you were headed towards Judgment?
舒服吗？
Comfortable?
你觉得自己够光荣能上天堂？
Feel like you were bound for glory?
还是有点担心会下地狱？
Or were you a little worried that you were going down?
我是这么认为的
I thought so.
你很幸运 尼克
You're lucky, Nick.
你有我们想要的技能
You have skills that we want.
所以我们给你一个选择
So we're giving you a choice.
你可以选择受审判
You can take your chances with Judgment,
或
or,
你可以加入RIPD
you can join the R.I.P.D.
什么RIPD？
The R.I.P.D?
冥界警察局
Rest In Peace Department.
我懂了 好名字
I get it. It's cute.
简单地说
Simply put,
我们专捉那些设法逃脱审判的死人
we find dead people that have managed to escape Judgment.
送他们回到属于他们的地方
We ship them off back down to where they belong.
这合约是100年期限
The tour is 100 years.
如果你答应了
If you say yes,
我们可以把你送回波士顿 你的老家
we'll send you back down to Boston, your home turf.
我答应
I'll do it.
这行不通的
That's not gonna work.
什么行不通？我说了我加入
What's not gonna work? I said I'm in.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
你耍赖 你想要回以前的生活
You got rooked, you want your old life back.
你想要朱莉娅
You want Julia.
不是 你问我能否加入
No. You asked me to help you,
我说我能加入
and I'm here to help.
你真的以为我看不穿你吗？
You really don't think I can read you?
这里有关于你的一切资料
I know everything there is to know about you.
千万别浪费这个机会 尼克
Don't squander this opportunity, Nick.
而且我肯定你会需要一封好的
I know for a fact you can use a good
推荐信去参加审判日的 对吧？
recommendation on Judgment Day, okay?
我觉得我提起了你的兴趣了
I think you're smelling what I'm selling.
还有其他问题吗？
Any more questions?
这是史提利丹乐团的什么歌？
What's with the Steely Dan?
我不知道  总是在唱
No idea. It's always playing.
使人轻松的
It seems to relax people.
- 开始吧  - 很好 开始了
- Let's do this. - Yes, let's.
可能会有点痛
This will tickle a bit.
冥界警局
警察
什么…
What the...
拿上东西 过来这里！
Clench 'em and get over here.
嘿 你是我的律师吗？
Hey, are you my lawyer?
肃静！
Settle down!
这儿是扣押室 我们称他们为“腐尸”
This is holding. We call them "Deados."
直到消亡前 他们看起来都像人
Until they pop, they look like regular people,
只有我们知道他们实为怪物
so no one except us knows they're monsters inside.
你看 如果从这里偷偷溜走了
You see, if you slip through the cracks
死后还留在人间的话
and stay on Earth after you die,
你灵魂会腐烂
your soul rots.
灵魂腐烂了 全世界都腐烂了
If they rot, the world rots.
全球变暖 黑死病
Global warming, black plague,
手机信号中断 明白了吗？
bad cell reception, get it?
没有RIPD
Without the R.I.P.D. ,
世界早就会在1954年
the world would have been overrun
被这些死人占领了
by these dead people some time in 1954.
用什么办法留下来的？
How is staying an option?
每天有150000人死亡
A hundred-and-fifty-thousand people die every day.
系统本身的设计是应付不了这个数量的
This system wasn't designed to handle that kind of volume.
欢迎加入大家庭
Welcome to the big league.
波士顿的冥界警局
R.I.P.D. Boston.
在你生前成为警务人员之前
Before you are the greatest law officers who ever lived and died.
我们已是第三大警局
We're the third biggest precinct in the force.
第一大是？
What's the first?
博卡区（阿根廷一港口）
Boca.
斯科茨代尔是第二
R.I.P.D. Scottsdale does a lot of volume, too.
相信我 胸毛的回头率很高的
Trust me, chest hair is making a big comeback.
我告诉你 女孩子喜欢它
I'm telling you, chicks dig it.
死后第一天要学习这些是有点多了
It's a lot to take in on your first day dead.
不过放心 你的搭档会解释一切
But don't worry, your partner will explain it all to you.
不！放开你的手！
No! Get your hands off me!
我告诉你 别用你那脏手
I said, get your hands
触摸
off
我！
me!
别这样 罗伊！
Come on, Roy.
别你个头
You come on.
只因为我是唯一敢开枪见血
Just because I'm the only one willing to lethal-up.
天呀
Jesus.
不 天你个头！
No, you Jesus!
- 罗伊！ - 什么？
- Roy!       - What?
他都走到门口了
He was going for the door.
如果你不满意 那我就光用枪指着他们得了
I'll plant a gun on him if it makes you feel any better.
你想不想把问题闹到“永恒部门”？
Would you like to take this up with Eternal Affairs?
我们都知道事实并非如此 亲爱的？
We both know what this is about, don't we, honey pot?
不是时候 罗伊
Not the time, Roy.
为什么不是现在呢？我很冷静
Why not have it out now? I'm comfortable.
罗伊 见见你的新搭档 尼克・沃克
Roy, meet your new partner, Nick Walker.
我们之前已经讨论过这个问题 我是独行侠
We've been over this before. I'm a one-man operation.
你别无选择 罗伊
Not a choice, Roy.
不 你需要争取
No. You gotta earn that.
来吧 菜鸟
Come on, rookie.
抓紧你的蛋蛋
Grab your huevos.
请遵循所有的已公告的规则
Please follow all posted regulations.
部门卫生规则是为大家利益着想
Department hygiene regulations are for your benefit.
来吧 别害羞
Tuck on in. Don't be shy.
RIPD警员返回工作岗位前应洗手
享受这次旅行吧
Goin' for a ride.
你们想过要更好地隐藏这个地方吗？
You ever think about hiding this place a little better?
你最后一次送修录像机是何时？
When was the last time you got a VCR repaired?
明白了
Point taken.
是的 你回来了
That's right, you're back.
不要弄湿裤子 来吧
Don't wet your pants over it. Come on.
我们要迟到了
Don't wanna be late.
监察员希望你先来个了结
Proctor likes to start you off with some closure.
上车！
Get in!
令人失望的出席者 是吧？
Disappointing turnout, huh?
应该更多些
Expected more.
我们有很多话要谈
We got a lot to talk about,
但现在我先停止一会儿
but for now, I'm just gonna step back,
你就沉思一分钟吧
let you soak it in for a minute.
此刻不是关于我的
This moment is not about me.
是关于你的
This is about you
想开点
letting go.
感谢你让我沉思
Thank you for letting me soak it in.
- 我在那里等着  - 好吧
- I'll wait for you. - All right.
你知道我的葬礼是怎么样？
Do you know what my funeral was?
看着一群土狼啃光我的尸体
Watching a bunch of coyotes pick my carcass clean
之后把我的骨头拖进一个山洞里
and drag my bones off into a cave.
一个该死的洞穴
A freaking cave, hoss.
好 来了
Here it comes.
要小心啊！
Be careful, now!
朱莉娅？朱莉娅！
Julia? Julia!
我在这里 我不知道怎么解释 但我在这里
I'm here. I don't know how, but I'm here.
对不起 我不认识你
I'm sorry, I don't know you.
能说几句吗？
Can we just talk?
别碰我… 走开好吗？
Please don't touch me... .go somewhere?
朱莉娅？ 嘿 朱莉娅！
Julia? Hey, Julia!
你怎么啦？
What's your problem, huh?
你个王八蛋
You piece of shit.
离开这里 放松一下
Get out of here. Just relax.
别忘了吃药啊 伙计
Get back on the meds, buddy.
- 把他弄出去！  - 把他弄出去！
- Get him out of here! - Get him out of here!
让我走！
Let me go!
真好吧
That went well.
看我多为你设想
I tried to do something nice for you.
到底发生了什么事？
What just happened?
为什么她不认识我？
How could she not know it was me?
因为在他们看来 你外表不像你
To them, you don't look like you,
你声音不像你
you don't sound like you.
如果你试着告诉他们真相
If you try to tell 'em who you are,
你的言词会化为胡言乱语
it comes out all garbled up.
宇宙的最高智慧
The universe, in its ultimate wisdom,
不会让你表露身份
will not let you reveal yourself.
他们比我们聪明
It's smarter than us.
太恶了
That's sick.
把它当作是宇宙版的保护证人计划吧
Consider it the universe's witness protection program.
那么 我是什么样子？
So, what do I look like?
给你
Here.
这些是你的身份证
These are your IDs.
几个联邦 很多部门 方便我们行事的
Some federal. A lot of utilities. Whatever gets us access.
不会吧？一个中国老头？
Really? An old Chinese guy?
那么你呢？
What about you?
那你赢了 罗伊
Well, I guess you win, Roy.
我来为你加快进度吧
Let me bring you up to speed with what's on my plate.
你跟我并肩同行 是你最好的选择
When you ride with me, you ride with the best.
步伐要快 期望值要高
The pace is lightning, expectations high.
事情往往来得又快又急 可能又热
Things are gonna come at you fast, they're gonna come hot,
可能又湿
and they're gonna come wet.
湿？
Wet?
怎么开的车 白痴！
Learn to drive, bimbo!
你以前开过车吗？学驾照了么？
You've done this before? Driving?
先教你我们这行基本做事方式#
You're gonna get your feet wet with a standard pickup.
发现犯罪嫌疑人 并试探他
Find the suspect and then test him.
看看他是不是个腐尸
See if he's a Deado.
然后…
And then...
瞧那女孩的脚踝
Look at the ankles on that girl.
那就是你喜欢的… 脚踝？
That's what you're into, ankles?
那个能让你兴奋？
That's what does it for you?
我那时代的女人 她们穿得很保守
In my day, women, they dressed very conservatively.
这就少了很多尴尬
That makes you way less creepy.
你那时是什么时候？
When exactly was your day?
18世纪 老兄
1800s, buddy.
我们的工作那时叫“执法官”
I'm what we used to call a "lawman."
马歇尔・罗伊史费斯・普尔斯菲
Marshal Roicephus Pulsipher.
“罗伊史费斯”？
"Roicephus"?
当时被认为是个性感的名字
It was considered a very sexy name at the time.
听起来像是某种性病
It sounds like an STD.
能小心点开车吗？
Would you care to drive?
我没有偷窥你妻子的脚
I didn't get a peek at your wife's ankles.
别再提起她了
Not one more word about her.
听着 菜鸟
Listen, rook.
你最好和她保持一定距离
You better work on getting a little distance,
因为你俩的事已结束了
because you two are over.
还是考虑你自己吧 搭档
You just worry about yourself, partner.
你不是我的搭档 菜鸟
You ain't my partner, rook.
你只是旁边座位上的混球 直到我认可你
You're just the ass in the other seat until I say contrary.
我曾有个搭档
I had a partner.
是我见过最棒的人
Greatest man I ever knew.
直到我背部中了他一枪
Right up until he shot me in the back.
这就是“搭档”会做的事
That's what "partner" will get you.
跟我说说 你觉得我是如何来到这里的？
Tell me about it. How do you think I got here?
你被一颗现代的子弹枪杀
You got shot with a modern bullet.
我喜欢现代的子弹 至少比较卫生
I would've loved a modern bullet. Sanitary, at least.
对啊 我觉得它穿越我脸时的感觉
That's exactly how it felt as it passed through my face.
真卫生啊
Sanitary.
“搭档”两字和我一起死了
The term "partner" died when I did.
明白了 罗伊屎忽屎
You got it, Roicephus.
- 罗伊史费斯  - 罗伊屎忽屎？
- "Roicephus."   - Roicephus.
叫我“罗伊”好了
Just call me "Roy."
我本想如此
I was gonna do that.
或“史费斯”
Or "Cephus."
现在听着
Now, listen up.
这是一个战术 菜鸟
This is tactical, rook.
战术？印度食品？
Tactical? A bag of Indian food?
没错  有线人说这楼里可能有一具腐尸
Yeah. I got a tip on a possible Deado in this building.
现在 边听边学
Now, listen and learn.
腐尸会放出一种坏死巫术
Deados put off a bad dead mojo.
用灵魂阴气感染周围的一切
Infect everything with their soul stank.
令一切都更糟
Infect everything for the worse.
对人和事物都有害
People and things.
注意看 腐尸会损坏东西 这就是痕迹
There you go. Broken shit is a dead giveaway.
灵魂杀手
Soul killers.
开枪射击它们的头部
Hit a Deado in the head with one of these,
必须是头部…
and it's got to be the head...
我个人更喜欢射脸
Personally, I find the face most gratifying.
灵魂就会被消灭
he's erased from the cosmos.
子弹不会伤害活人 却会伤害我们
Won't hurt live ones, will hurt us.
所以小心别走火
So, you be extra careful where you point that thing.
枪械安全 我很在行
I'm pretty solid on gun safety.
我看到你脚踝上绑的东西了
I saw that ankle piece you're strapping.
那些人间武器没有作用
Live-world gun don't do diddly-squat here.
把你眼睛远离我的脚踝 谢谢
You can keep your eyes off my ankles, thank you.
让我们来看看是什么事
Watch me sniff this out.
相当明显了
Even more promising.
一向都是最安静的那个
It's always the quiet one.
你准备好了吗？上好了弹？
You ready? You pumped?
我需要你专心抓猎物 抓雪人
I need you all here. Get your snowman on, get frosty.
警戒 冰火
Alert, icy-hot.
你是不是尽力表现得像个警察？
Is this you trying to sound like a cop?
我感觉到你有点在装腔作势#
Because it throws up a lot of red flags for me.
你该学点行话
You gotta learn the lingo, hombrito.
我准备好了 不用担心
I'm frosty. Don't worry about it.
高级警员才能先出手 菜鸟
Senior officer gets to knock, rook.
我之前做了15年的警察
I've got 15 years on the force.
别再叫我“菜鸟”那种废话
Knock off the "rookie" bullshit.
你从警多年？
You've done this before?
知不知道门后在等你的是什么？
You know what's waiting for you behind the door?
你可以把15年警察经验放到马桶冲走
You can take your 15 years, you can flush it down the toilet,
因为现在情况不同
because this ain't that.
我敲门 你展示证件
I knock, you do the cards.
史丹利・纳维奇
Stanley Nawicki.
我们是卫生部门的
We're with the Department of Health.
有什么问题吗？
Is there a problem?
是这样的 纳维奇先生
Well, Mr. Nawicki,
我们怀疑你已死了
we suspect that you might be dead.
这真的有必要吗？
Is this really necessary?
无意冒犯 但这听起来真疯狂
No offense, but you sound kind of crazy.
我们不介意
None taken.
这只是个例行检查 完事后走人
Just a routine test and we'll be out of your hair.
但我没死啊
I am not dead.
我是说 检查我的脉搏 来啊！
I mean, Check my pulse, go ahead!
菜鸟 第一个问题
Rook, first question.
“在一个圣灰星期三晚上”(基督教圣日)
"It's late on Ash Wednesday.
“一位开旧的阿库拉车的亚洲年轻人”
"An Asian teenager in a slammed-out Acura
“请你吃一盘咖哩鸡”
"offers you a plate of chicken vindaloo.
“你会不会接受？”
"Do you accept?"
我应该如何应对？
How am I supposed to answer that?
你告诉我
You tell me.
好吧 答案是不
Okay, the answer is no.
这是什么原因？是不是这个年轻人？
What's the problem? Is it the teenager?
圣灰日？
The ash?
还是日本车？
Is it the Japanese performance sedan?
也许是因为印度菜
Maybe it's the Indian food.
什么？
What?
也许你讨厌印度人
Maybe you hate Injuns.
不 那实在…
No. That's...
卡片(下一题)
Card.
“年轻人是亚美尼亚人 那一天是犹太新年”
"The teenager is Armenian. The day is Rosh Hashanah.
“食物是印度咖哩菠菜干芝士”
"The dish is saag paneer."
我不想
I don't want it.
为什么？
Why not?
太辣了？太稀烂？
Too spicy? Too mushy?
你…
You...
- 在提问时你不能吃东西 - 我不想要…
- You can't eat during an interview. - I don't want...
不想要什么？
You don't what?
卡片！
Card!
“这车是黄绿色的丰田 季节是夏至”
"The car is a lime-green Scion. The season is the solstice.
“食物是伯爵咖哩沙律鸡肉丁”
"The dish is chicken tikka masala."
- 不  - 没错
- No.   - Yes.
- 不是  - 是的 就是咖哩鸡！
- No.             - Yes, it is!
盘里就是咖哩鸡！盘里就是咖哩鸡！
The dish is chicken tikka! The dish is chicken tikka!
是的 这是一具腐尸
Yeah, that's a Deado.
大嘴出现了
Big old mouth coming in.
他生前是告密者 (死后成大嘴怪)
Feller was a snitch in life.
看吧 尼克 就像这 充满讽刺性
See, Nick? Like that. Metaphorical.
出于某种原因 印度食物似乎有关键作用
For some reason, Indian food seems to do the trick.
也许是小茴香
Maybe it's the cumin.
可以动手拿他了 我请客
You can bag this one. My treat.
不 我才不想靠近这东西
No. I'm not going near that.
你那15年的功力现在在哪里了？
Where's that 15 years now, frosty?
你需要习惯犯人的样子和味道
You gotta get comfortable with the visuals and the smell profile.
- 好吧  - 去啊！
- All right.  - Go on!
张开双手 快点 去那里
Spread 'em. Come on, let's go.
快点 去冰柜那里站好
Hurry up, let's get this over with.
一旦他们现形后 他们就知道要结束了
Once they pop, they know it's over.
对吧 老兄？
Right, pal?
把手放后背
Put all your hands behind your back.
这愚蠢的宇宙手铐
Stupid space cuffs.
不！
No!
你很想要吗？？
You want it?
给你了！
You got it!
尼克！抓住他！
Nick! Grab him!
抓住他剩下的部份！
Get the rest of him!
控制住！
Contain!
天啊
Holy shit.
蠢材 别动！
Giddyup, pony!
不 不！
No, no!
保持身体放松！
Relax your body!
什么？
What?
身体放松！
Relax body!
给我一个理由
Give me a reason.
不需要是个好理由
Doesn't have to be a good one.
其实也不需要有什么意义
Actually, doesn't even have to make sense.
很有趣 对吧？
Fun, right?
你或者已经发现我们身体很能受撞击
You might have noticed we're pretty durable.
它依然很痛
It still hurts.
那就是菜鸟要垫底的原因
That's why rook's the bottom.
垫底
Bottom.
垫底！
Bottom!
好吧
Okay.
我认为这在情绪上是可以理解的
I guess that's emotionally understandable.
你真的要检查那些东西吗？
You're really gonna rummage through that?
行动后的简报
Brief after-action report.
你在房间中表现欠佳
Now, you were below average in the room,
但飞行时对我的操纵反应良好
but you did respond well to my steering during the airborne portion.
你的身体令我成功软着陆
Your internal organs provided me a very soft landing.
缓冲效果很令人满意
You have a very impressive crumple zone.
不好的地方就是让你自己
With the exception of letting yourself
直接面对腐尸的攻击…
get attached directly to the beastie...
闭嘴！
Stop talking.
你整体算好 给你C+
you were solid. C-plus.
闭嘴
Stop talking.
- 只是完成评审工作  - 闭嘴 闭嘴！
- Just doing my job. - Stop it. Stop talking!
是你一直在说啊
You're the one who's talking.
在我葬礼上你就说个不停
You ran your mouth at my funeral.
你把我推下楼时也说个不停
You ran your mouth when you pushed me out of a building,
还用我的身体当垫子
and used my body as a cushion.
从我俩见面开始就一直废话连篇！
You've run your mouth non-stop since the minute we met!
我想我明白这是怎么回事了
I think I know what's going on here.
不 不 不！ 闭嘴！！闭嘴 让我来处理了
No, no, no! Shut up! You shut up and let me deal.
好 你来处理一地呕吐物
All right, you deal. Deal with the upchuck.
再细想一下 就冲你这个态度
Come to think of it, with all this tantrumery,
我开始觉得也许我有点太慷慨了
I'm beginning to think that I might have been a little too generous
要是给你个C+的话
with the "plus" on that C.
降一点比较好
I might just have to lower your grade.
身体放松啊
Relax body.
我的帽子！
My hat!
新评分 F！（不及格）
New grade. F!
巴士的事 我能原谅你
The bus, I can forgive.
但我的帽子 现在我连提都不想提
My hat? I can't even talk about that now.
去 去 去！时间是关键 走吧
Let's go, go, go! Time is a factor. Let's go.
到底搞什么呢？消防演习？
What the hell is this? A fire drill?
我从来没有见过这样的事
I never seen it this busy.
似乎上周所有腐尸全来波士顿了
Seems like every Deado moved to Boston last week.
我怎么说的？快回到岗位上
What did I say? Get back out there.
不许任何人出去 直到事态被控制住
No breaks for anyone until this surge is under control.
如果不是我需要你在街上的话…
If I didn't need you back on the streets...
如何？你踢我屁股吗？
What? You'd have my ass?
别在陈词滥调了
Don't be a cliche.
你放任他由窗户跳出去了
You let him get out the window.
你是不是做的比这更好？
Aren't you better than that?
是你把训练菜鸟的活儿丢给我的
You're the one who put me with training wheels, here.
继续啊 作秀啊 当老板嘛
But go on, make a show. Be the boss.
你还是和“老板”相处不好 是不是？
You still have a hard time with the "boss" part, don't you?
游戏你玩过了 得到你想要的了
You played the game, got what you wanted.
我不玩游戏
I don't play the game.
我的屁股是我的 只属于我的！
And my ass is mine and mine alone!
眼巴巴地看着呢！
Eagerly noted!
拜托 反正你屁股也不正
Come on. It's flat, anyway.
罗伊 纳维奇誓死保护这块金子
Roy, Nawicki was trying awfully hard to protect this gold.
你不觉得我们应该搞清楚是怎么回事吗？
Don't you think we should try to figure out what it is?
相信我 无事可查
Trust me, it's nothing.
这种事百分之九十九是
Ninety-nine percent of these things are just
各种宗教类的筹款物品
fundraising items for various religions.
一堆废物
Just crap.
那百分之一呢？
What about the one percent?
那就是我们把它们锁在这里的原因
That's why we lock them up in here.
打个包 标记一下 深藏起来
Bag it, tag it and bury it deep.
- 这是全部了吗？  - 没错
- Is that all of it? - That's it.
请在这里签名
Sign here, please.
罗伊 听我说
Roy, listen.
什么？
What?
纳维奇极其在意那块金子黄金
Nawicki cared an awful lot about that gold.
是啊
Yeah.
他试图对我们有所隐藏 为什么？
He was trying to hide it from us. Why?
现在 你倒是相当热心了？
So, now you're all gung-ho, huh?
我觉得应该追查下去
I'm thinking we should follow up.
让我猜猜 天才已有计划了
Let me guess. Genius has a plan.
天才觉得我们应到外面去查一查
Genius wants to get out on the street and work this.
我觉得你可以帮我
I think that you can help me with that.
你知道吗？
You know why?
因为每个我认识的好警察
Because every great cop that I've ever known
都会有一个线人
has their own informant.
大罗伊…
Big Roy...
大罗伊 他会有一个的
Big Roy, he's gotta have one.
你想要线人吗？
You want an informant?
大罗伊有最好的线人
Big Roy's got the best informant.
现在击球的是红袜队的34号 大卫・奥提兹
Now batting for the Red Sox, number 34, David Ortiz.
艾略特 他是一个难缠的腐尸
Elliot. He's a pain-in-the-ass Deado.
但他只关心红袜队
All he cares about is the Sox.
所以我留他在人间打探消息
So, I let him stick around in exchange for information.
你的
Here.
人在早上会有个大洞要填
You're in mourning. You got a hole to fill.
我没有感觉到味道啊
You know, I can't taste anything.
当然没有 你死了啊
Of course not, you're dead.
RIPD探员不吃 也不睡
R.I.P.D. don't eat, we don't sleep.
我们的存在只为处理腐尸
You're here to kick Deado ass, that's about it.
那么你为什么吃它？
Then why would you eat this?
我喜欢那口感
I enjoy the mouth feel.
近来怎么样 艾略特？
How's it going, Elliot?
我们领先
We're up.
但比赛打得真烂 我们搞砸了
But they're hitting like crap. We'll blow it.
随你便
Knock yourself out.
你好 艾略特
Hello, Elliot.
你的某个朋友要舍身保护这个东西
One of your buddies was willing to get erased for this.
为什么？
Why?
菜鸟
Rook.
那是物证部门的事
That belongs in evidence.
我以为你具有某种反叛精神的 罗伊
I thought you were some kind of rebel, Roy.
我为北方联军打过仗
I fought for the North.
你不介意我回去调查吧？
Would you mind terribly if I got back to my investigation?
继续调查吧
Go continue your investigation.
告诉我这是什么 艾略特
Tell me what this is, Elliot.
它看起来像一块巨大的黄金
That looks like a big hunk of gold.
回答不满意 请再试一次
That's not gonna cut it. Try again.
放开你的手！
Get your hands off me!
你好自为之吧 艾略特
You behave yourself now, Elliot.
是因为我 所以你现在才坐得舒服
Because of me, you're sitting there all cozy
而不是躺在棺材里
and not lying in a pine box.
也不是走过沙漠
Not walking the desert,
想从一只土狼那里寻回你的骨头
trying to get your femur back from a coyote.
你们这些警察都是一个样子
You cops are all the same.
总是念念不忘如何勒索别人
Always obsessing about how you bit it.
你的葬礼怎么样 菜鸟？
How was your funeral, newbie?
你妻子接到美丽的国旗时 你哭了吗？
Did you cry when they gave your wife that nice folded-up flag?
很有趣 对吧？
That's fun, right?
你该很清楚
I think we both know
那个世界里是没有红袜队的
there's no Red Sox on the other side,
你为什么不合作呢？
so why don't you cooperate?
我为我的态度道歉
I apologize for my poor attitude.
我可以仔细看看吗 先生？
May I take a closer look, sir?
当然
You may.
抱歉让你失望 但这只是件废物
Look, I'm sorry to disappoint, but this is crap.
听着 腐尸也很情绪化的
Look, Deados, they're sentimental.
很多都会相信这种护身符之类的废物
A lot of them believe in this talismanic junk.
如果这有用
If it was something else,
外面必然有人宣扬了
there'd be some chatter out there.
那我就会知道
I would know.
好 我们走吧
All right, we're done here.
这帽子糟透了
These hats are crap.
帮我多留意这件事
Keep your ears open for me.
好的 警官
Yes, sir.
你把黄金给了他？
You gave him the gold?
没看到他很紧张吗？我看穿了他
Did you see him squirm? We got him.
“看穿了”？什么意思 我们有吗？
"Got him"? What do you mean, "we got him"?
哪里得手了？
What did we get?
告诉你他拿了什么 他拿走了黄金！
Tell you what he got, he got the gold!
是你给他的！
Which you gave him!
你这到底是怎么了？
What the hell is the matter with you?
我着急我的帽子
I'm pissed about my hat.
那好吧 快瞧 快瞧
Well, then. Looky, looky.
我要教你什么叫现代执法
I'm gonna treat you to a little modern law enforcement.
这就是所谓的“丢狗骨头”
This is called "giving the dog a bone."
骨头？
Bones?
他这是干嘛？
What's he doing?
好吧 感觉很怪
Okay, that's weird,
因为他看起来很像你的前任搭档
because that looks exactly like your ex-partner.
枪杀你的那个人
The one who shot you dead.
好吧 我感兴趣了 很感兴趣
Okay, I'm interested. Color me interested.
我觉得你受刺激了 是吧？
This must be chafing you, huh?
首先 这家伙追踪你就像闻到了一根香肠
First, the guy smoked you like a knockwurst,
然后他找人拿走你的黄金
and now he's got guys just handing him gold.
让我想想 让我想想
Let me think, just let me think.
这有什么好想的？
What's there to think about?
这家伙是在训练你往左往右
The man's just schooling you left and right.
你自己的搭档
Your own partner.
一箭三雕
And the trifecta.
与你妻子上床
Sleeping with your wife.
这是你的房子 是不是？
Because this is your house, isn't it?
活活的屈辱啊
Total humiliation.
就像脱了裤子在市场上瞎跑
It's just a pants-down spanking in the supermarket.
他不会和朱莉娅睡的
He's not sleeping with Julia.
想打赌吗？
Want to bet?
好 来吧
Yeah, let's.
赢家可随便打输家的脸
Winner shoots the loser in the face
多少次都可以
as many times as he wants.
我不是百分百对我的判断有自信的
I'm not 100 percent confident with my read.
迈克店的卡诺里煎饼
Some cannolis from Mike's.
以前尼克经常让我停下来专门为你买
I was thinking how Nick used to make us stop and get them for you.
谢谢 谢谢你 鲍比
Thank you. Thank you, Bobby.
嘿 朱莉娅 你认为尼克以前还好吗？
Hey, Julia, did Nick seem all right to you?
我意思是 他有担心什么吗？
I mean, was he concerned about anything?
没有
No.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
为什么呢？
Why?
很抱歉我提起这事
I'm sorry I got to do this now.
尼克说他埋葬了一些东西
Nick said he buried something.
若他不是为了上床
If he's not sleeping with her,
来这里就太奇怪了 对不对？
it's kind of funny he's here, isn't it?
或是你们约好晚死者要帮另一人
Unless you guys have a pact where he
清理电脑里的色情片
scrubs the porn off your laptop for you.
这我理解
I get that.
事实上 太经典了
Classy, actually.
他给了我这个 他知道我想要什么
He gave this to me. He knew I wanted it.
如你所言
What are you saying,
他这样做 是想在底下藏些什么？
that he just did this to hide something under it?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是 我必须看看
But I've got to take a look.
我真希望是我错了
I was hoping I was wrong.
真的？他偷的？
Really? He stole this?
天啊 我觉得恶心
God, I feel sick.
你个王八蛋
You crooked son of a bitch.
你要到何时才告诉我呢？
When were you gonna tell me about this?
- 放下枪  - 闭嘴
- Put the gun down. - Shut up.
把它们带走吧 我不想见到它们
Just get it away from me. I don't want to see it.
别担心 什么都不需要担心
Don't worry. Don't worry about a thing.
他是我最好的朋友
He was my best friend.
我甚至不知道他是谁
I don't even know who he was.
放开我 否则我打断你的腿
Get off of me or I'll break your legs.
现在给我个解释！
Explanation, now!
我们从一群小混混手中得到那些黄金
We took something from a bunch of shit-rats
他们原是想利用它换枪支和毒品什么的
who would have turned it into guns or drugs or who knows what.
这是没有受害者的犯罪 就这样而已
It was a victimless crime. End of story.
那腐尸拿它干嘛？
Why would the Deados want it?
你以为海耶斯和我知道那腐尸要干什么吗？
You think Hayes and I knew about this Deado shit?
对我来说那只是金钱
It was just money to me.
我只是想让日子过得更好点
I was trying to make our life better.
你的工作是干得不错 对吧？
Well, you did a good job of that, didn't you?
你为什么不再试试中国佬那一招呢？
Why don't you go try the Chinaman thing again?
跟她解释一下 绝对实用啊
Explain it to her. That went well.
再来啊 如果能让你…
Try it again if it makes you...
黄金要逃了
Gold's getting away.
来吧 别紧张
Come on, tighten up.
我妻子认为我是个混蛋
My wife sees me as a piece of shit.
事实上 她把你当成个中国佬
Actually, she sees you as an old Chinese guy.
不过 陈大爷外表忠厚老实
And by the way, Grandpa Chen's a pretty solid look.
对监视有帮助
Helps with stakeouts.
我只在乎她怎么看我
The only thing that I ever cared about is what she thought of me.
这是唯一重要的事
That's all that matters. The only thing.
她对我的印象和看法
What she thinks, that's who I am.
而我搞砸了 毁掉了一切
And I blew that. Destroyed it.
呜呼
Boo-hoo.
说什么？
Excuse me?
你听到的 哭泣吧
You heard me. Boo-de-hoo.
你是我见过的最糟糕的人
You might be the worst person I've ever met.
不幸的是 你不能告诉她
Sadly, you do not get to tell her
你的所作所为全是为了她
how you did it all for her.
你觉得这是天大的悲剧
And where exactly do you think your tragedy ranks
那宇宙正义在哪里？
on the scales of cosmic injustice?
那巴基斯坦地震又如何？
Pakistan-earthquake level?
- 那杀人战场又如何？  - 这对我个人是很重要的
- Killing Fields level? - For me, it was pretty big.
你以为你是唯一一个发生这种情况的人？
You think you're the only one who was cut down in his prime?
你以为我没有感觉了
You don't think I felt unresolved
当我的脸被一只秃鹫吞噬吗？
as my face was being devoured by a buzzard?
神啊
Christ.
你必须学会承受痛苦和悔恨
You are just gonna have to learn to sit on your regret and pain
直到转化为一种单调的持续的疼痛为止
until it turns into a dull, persistent ache.
我是那样做的 这才是男人的做法
The way I do it. The way a man does it.
我是拍音乐录影带的
I do music videos.
私人电话号码在背面
Home phone number's on the back.
什么？
Excuse me?
我来地球上不是作为一块肉
I'm not a piece of meat put on this earth
去让您满足的
for your gratification.
我是个女人
I'm a woman.
放尊重些 不然我就阉了你
Respect me, or I will castrate you
把你变回3岁小孩
like a three-year-old steer.
看起来很好 我们有收获了
Look sharp. We got something.
是的 这是一具腐尸
Yeah, that's a Deado.
这人应该是海耶斯的销赃犯
That has got to be Hayes' fence.
- 我们跟着黄金走  - 我明白了
- We stay on the gold. - I got this.
等下 让你老爹我先去
Hold up. Daddy's on point.
不 谢了 我看过你怎么行动了
No thanks, I've seen you in action.
你在质疑我的方法吗？
You questioning my methods?
你根本没有方法
You don't have a method.
打扰了 先生 就说几句话
Excuse me, sir. A quick word?
去冷冻室
Freezer.
小茴香种子
让我来开门
Allow me.
我的错
My bad.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
RIPD 对不对？
R.I.P.D. , huh?
外观不错啊！
Great looks, man!
你和你的熊猫快餐都在这儿
You, with your Panda Express over there.
别说种族笑话
Easy with the racial.
你 和你的…
And you, with your...
小心点！
Watch it!
难以置信的豪乳
magnificent breasts.
嘿 络腮胡 告诉我们有关黄金的事
Hey, sideburns, tell us about the gold.
瞧啊 在这里大家都是朋友
Look, we're all friends here.
来个互相帮助
Let's help each other out.
你不想现形
You don't want to get popped,
我也不想强迫你现形
and I don't want to pop you.
- 你不想？  - 不想
- You don't?    - No.
所以你只要把箱子给我们
So you're just gonna give us that case,
之后谈一谈
you're gonna start talking,
然后你可以继续四处逛逛
and then you get to keep roaming around
还保留着你的骚胡须
with your bitchin' ginger sideburns.
你知道吗？
You know what?
我厌倦了躲藏
I'm sick of hiding.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
那再好不过了！
That's better!
好吧 我们来吧！
Hell, yeah. Let's do this!
控制住！
Contain!
控制不住！
Didn't contain!
去你的
Suck it.
正中屁股！
Straight butt!
看吧！
Come on!
马术表演时刻
It's rodeo time.
老爹要玩绳子了！
Pappy's got some roping to do!
帮个小忙怎么样？
How about a little help?
好吧
Okay.
你没事吧？找人拨打911！
Are you okay? Somebody call 911!
我没事 没有什么可看的
I'm okay. Nothing to see.
我得走了！
Got to go!
头部！目标是射头部！
The head! Aim for the head!
还在这里 狗娘养的！
Still here, you son of a bitch!
我的屁股啊！
My ass!
这是什么？
What is that?
借过！
Coming through!
对不起 原谅我
Excuse me, pardon me.
我来了！
Here I come!
放松身体
Relax body.
菜鸟！
Rook!
在这里！
Over here!
他弄出太多麻烦了
If it's not too much trouble.
非常感谢你
Thank you very much.
我从来没见过像这样的事
I've never seen one like that before.
从来没有！
Never!
这从来没有发生过！
Never before has this happened!
恭喜 伙计们 弄出这一堆烂摊子！
Congratulations, guys, on your unprecedented cock-up!
好吧！
All right!
你让一只现形的腐尸
You let an exposed Deado loose
光天化日出现在街上
on the streets in the middle of the day.
本来可以控制的
You were supposed to contain.
这是最基本的任务
That is your most basic job.
那东西失控了
There was no containing that thing.
但你们却大大地失败了
And you failed spectacularly to contain.
他说得对 小甜心 这一次是不同的
He's right, sweetie pie. It was different.
我们有证据
We have evidence.
没有调查任务
You don't investigate,
不需要这么有创意
you don't get creative.
只需按章做事
You do as you're told.
否则 就会发生这种情况
When you don't, this happens.
令人恐惧
It was terrifying.
暴走在波士顿街上的不是人类
Whatever rampaged through the streets of Boston today was not human.
现在看看我们在哪里
Now look where we are.
你需要与他们打交道
You get to deal with them.
说了半天 到底谁是“他们”？
Who in this endless stream of freaks is "them"?
永恒部门 锤子从天而落
Eternal Affairs. The hammer's dropping.
怎么样？
Well?
他们很生气 理所当然的
They're pissed. Justifiably.
但是 明显地
However, apparently,
看来你们的确撞上一些重要的事情
you stumbled upon something important.
别那么惊讶 亲爱的
Don't act so surprised, honey pot.
普尔斯菲和沃克警官带来的那块黄金
The gold that officers Pulsipher and Walker brought in
是极其危险的神器的一部分
are part of an incredibly dangerous artifact
称为“杰里科权杖”
known as the Staff of Jericho.
废话
Crap.
能为菜鸟讲解下是怎么回事吗？
Maybe feather it in for the new guy a little bit?
你还记得你死时经过的隧道吗？
Remember the tunnel we pulled you out of when you died?
这是获得来世的唯一方式
That's the only way to get to the afterlife.
它是一条单行道
It's a one-way street.
此神器如果建成了 能倒转隧道
This artifact, if built, reverses the tunnel.
让腐尸如下雨一样闯进人间
The dead rain down on the earth.
结束人类世界
That's it for the living world.
大规模破坏
Yeah, massive destruction.
我们在3000年前撞到过这件事
We broke it to pieces 3,000 years ago.
现在它回来了
Now it's back.
直到我们得到剩下的黄金为止
Until we get the rest of the gold,
我们处于红色警戒
we're on red alert.
而且很显然 需要“你敌人的血”
Also, apparently, you need "the blood of thine enemy."
还有一大堆图画
There are more diagrams.
什么？
Why?
为什么会有人做这样的东西？
Why would someone make something like that?
真是的！
Come on!
我在这里 希望能维护秩序
Here I am, willing the streets into order,
我努力工作一年又一年！
making headway, year after dominant year!
而现在我所做的一切处于威胁之中
And now, everything I've done is being threatened
就因为古代五千年前某傻瓜做的器物
because of some ancient totem forged for kicks
而前功尽弃吗？
by some asshole 5,000 years ago?
我为什么要再试？我的意思是我怎么做？
Why even try? I mean, how am I supposed to do it?
看看你 真为你骄傲
Look at you. So proud of yourself.
“我只得到另一个大桶子而已”
"I got an important tube."
什么？
What?
这是什么？
Well, what is it?
其实
Actually,
看来你们两个似乎可以
it looks like you two don't need to
不用担心红色警报了
concern yourselves with the red alert.
我很不高兴
It brings me no pleasure
通知你们 因为近期你们那史诗式的失败
to inform you that because of your recent epic failure,
你俩被停职 不能处理这案件了
you've both been suspended, you're off the case.
等一会 这是我们的案子
Hold on a sec, we are the case.
是我们把案件带给你的！
We're the ones who brought it in!
感觉就像是碰运气了
The feeling is that luck was involved.
明天将有个正式的听证会
There'll be a formal hearing tomorrow,
之后你们很可能会被删除
after which you'll most likely be erased.
“删除？”
"Erased"?
所以在这个危机时刻 我们要被停职
So in this moment of crisis, they're gonna suspend
然后再删除最优秀的警员？
and then erase their best officer?
还有这个家伙？
And this other guy?
还有更好的警官会来接手
Better officers are taking over.
没有的事 报个名吧
No such thing. Name one.
雅各森 杜博
Jacobson, DuBow.
- 沃特森 - 真可笑
- Waterson. - Come on.
卡森
Carson.
- 杰克逊  - 他算不错
- Jackson. - He's pretty good.
那在塔科工作的人
That guy who works at the taco cart.
- 要继续吗？  - 好吧 好吧！
- Shall I go on? - Okay, okay!
明天是我的最后一天？
Tomorrow is my last day?
很有可能
Most likely.
对不起
I'm sorry.
该死
Well, shit.
监察员女士 谢谢
Miss Proctor, it's been a delight.
罗伊 非常感谢你的指导
Roy, thank you very much for your mentorship.
我确信这对你也意义重大
I'm sure it meant a lot to you.
我需要去个更重要的地方
I got somewhere more important to be.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你为什么要跟着我？
Why are you following me?
不要靠近我
Stay away from me.
我一直没有离开过
I haven't left you.
是我
It's me.
不
No.
所以
So.
表示祝贺 你最终做到了
Congratulations. You finally did it.
你得到你想要的了？
You get what you wanted?
我或许明天被删除
I might get erased tomorrow.
你以为我会怎么做？
What do you think I'm gonna do?
你吓着她了 要是你没注意到的话
You're freaking her out, if you haven't noticed.
我不是来自于什么敏感与浪漫主义时代的人
I'm not from a time of sensitivities and emotionalism.
在我的时代 我花钱买我的钟点爱情
And yes, in my day, I bought my love by the hour.
但我知道 你做什么都不起作用的
But I do know that what you're doing is not helping.
这叫鬼痴迷 会造成她的痛苦
It's called haunting, hoss. You're causing her pain.
你觉得为什么我们在这里？
Why do you think we're here?
我们所做的是什么？
Why we do what we do?
就是令朱莉娅有个能够生存的世界
It's so that Julia can have a world to live in.
是啊 这代表没有你在
And, yeah, that means without you.
她需要忘掉你
She needs to survive you.
结交新友 重组新家庭
Meet someone new, maybe have a family.
因为你回不去了
Because you are not coming back.
永远
Ever.
你有的只是工作
The job is all you have now.
我们连工作都失去了
Well, we don't have the job anymore.
尼克
Nick.
放下你的情感 像我一样
Resolve your crap. Do like me.
像你？
Like you?
是的 效仿我的平静
Yes, emulate my peace.
这像佛法一样的心境？
Your Zen-like calm?
我花了很多时间才做到当前的这状态
It's taken me a very long time to achieve this state.
你也能做到 但你太弱了
You could get there, too, but for your weakness.
你知道吗？我受够了
You know what? I've had it.
我再也受不了听你嘴里蹦出自以为是的老掉牙的故事了
I can't listen to one more self-righteous chestnut out of your mouth.
我不想每天都听你那很奇怪的过去
I don't want to live in your weird past with you.
说起这个 那些土狼…
Speaking of which, those coyotes...
你小心点说话
You be careful now.
那些土狼啃你的骨头而且在你脸上拉屎？
Those coyotes who ate your bones and crapped out your face?
在这个故事中 土狼才是英雄
In that story, the coyotes are the heroes.
你也许认为旧西部全是狗屁
You may think the Old West was all shits and giggles,
全是荒草和便宜的妓女
and sarsaparilla and two-cent whores.
它就是！
It wasn't!
它是臭的 是暴力的
It was smelly, it was violent.
满地都是痢疾和不可靠的印弟安人
It was ridden with dysentery and no-account Injuns.
我曾经都充满怒气 明白吗？
I've had a lot of anger to get past, okay?
而你…
And you...
你呢 尼克 说这么多的废话
You, Nick, are bringing a lot of shit out
而我却压抑了很长时间！
that I've been suppressing for a very long time!
其中一只土狼
One of them coyotes,
用我的骷髅交配
he made love to my skull.
你知不知道那种行为通常叫做什么吗？
Do you know what that practice is commonly called?
我知道
I do.
我希望它能干你的双眼 罗伊
And I certainly hope he got both eyes, Roy.
# 言语 就像匕首刺伤我们的心 #
# Words, like daggers stab our heart #
# 孩子 #
# Boys #
# 得做个好男人 #
# Gotta be the better man #
这首歌被称为“好男人”
The song is called Better Man.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I got that.
# 有人可能伤了你的心 #
# PeopIe, they can break your heart #
# 孩子 #
# Boys #
# 就像从来没有小狼可以… #
# Like no coyote ever can... #
也许我有点太过分了
Maybe I took things a little too far.
“也许”？
"Maybe"?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你应该拿起一个乐器 尼克
You ought to take up an instrument, Nick.
也许你可以柔和悦耳地
It might be a tuneful way for you
渡过你的最后一刻
to spend what may be your last moments.
你对待工作是正确的 罗伊
You were right about the job, Roy.
我们应该回去了
We gotta get back out there.
不-可-能
"Sus-pen-dato."
如果想要我回去 他们应该要来求我
If they want me back, they're gonna have to beg.
我不要留下来等死 你呢？
I'm not gonna take this lying down. You?
要在这里消沉下去吗？
Are you gonna sit there and mope?
或者你想不想帮我停止这浩劫？
Or do you want to help me stop an apocalypse?
你居然把它说成这样
When you put it that way, hell,
你是要把我挤进死角
you kind of paint me into a corner.
我知道海耶斯坐拥一堆黄金
I know Hayes is sitting on some of that gold.
他不可能只是个交易者
There's no way he's just a bagman.
让我问你一件事
Let me ask you something.
他喜欢印度食物吗？
Did he like Indian food?
他不喜欢
He was not a fan.
但是我有点困惑
But something's bugging me.
我和这个家伙搭档都五年了
I rode with this guy for five years,
我没有发现任何“阴气重”的情况
I never noticed any kind of "soul stank."
我听说某种稀有护身符能掩盖阴气
I heard talk of a rare kind of artifact that could mask it.
像除臭剂 灵魂香水
Like a spiritual deodorant.
定是他随身佩戴的东西
It would be something he carried with him all the time.
祖母的圣克里斯多夫项链
Like Grandma's Saint Christopher medal.
就是那个了
That'd do her.
让我们令那混蛋现形吧
Let's go pop the son of a bitch.
你知道要做什么？
Do you know what to do?
是的 我等了很长一段时间了
Yeah. I've been waiting a long time for this.
你等了很长时间吗？
You've been waiting a long time?
你知道腐尸花了多少年要做成这件事吗？
Do you know how many years Deados have been trying to pull this off?
3000年
Three thousand.
这些废物没有一个能收集起所有的黄金
Not one of those jag-offs could get all that gold together,
直到我出现
until me.
RIPD根本不知道是什么重击了他们
R.I.P.D. is not gonna know what hit them.
现在你亲自去惹点麻烦
Now, go find yourself some trouble.
非常乐意
My pleasure.
你好 朱莉娅
Hey, Julia.
我想和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
我碰到了很奇怪的事情
Something really strange happened to me.
怎么回事呢？
What's going on?
我昨晚在跑道上
I was at the track last night,
你还记得葬礼上的那个家伙吗？
and do you remember that guy at the funeral?
小个子的中国佬？
The little Chinese guy?
大叫大闹的那个？
The one who was yelling?
慢慢说 慢慢说 深吸一口气
Slow down, slow down. Take a deep breath.
我不知道 我觉得
I don't know. Somehow, I feel like
那像是尼克试图跟我说话的感觉
it's Nick who's trying to talk to me.
好吧
Okay.
我知道这听起来很疯狂
I know it sounds crazy.
我知道你想念他 我也想念他
I know you miss him. I miss him, too.
我认为现在你不该独自去面对
I don't think you should be alone right now.
我去接你 一起吃个午饭
I'm gonna come pick you up, and I'm gonna take you to lunch
我们可以好好谈谈
and we could talk about everything.
好吗？
All right?
好吧
Okay.
好的 谢谢你帮助我
All right. Thank you for this.
应该的  回头见
Absolutely. I'll see you later.
你负责前面 我绕到后面
Take the front. I'll go around back.
看我的
Works for me.
鲍比・海耶斯？
Bobby Hayes?
什么事？
Yeah?
我要问你一些问题
I need to ask you a few questions
关于印度式粘土烤箱的问题
involving a tandoori clay oven.
宝贝 你可以问任何你想要的事情
Sweetheart, you can ask me anything you want.
请不要拘束
Make yourself comfortable.
喝一杯怎么样？
How about a little drinky-poo?
好的 让我润润嘴
Sure. I'll wet my beak.
马上就来
Coming right up.
你在找这个吗？
Are you looking for this?
身手不错啊
Nice moves,
尼克
Nick.
这外表不佳啊
Hey, tough look to pull off.
我已习惯了
I'm getting used to it.
你知道那只是个交易而已
You know, it was just business.
试试再动一下
Make a move, please.
放松点 尼克
Easy, Nick.
“在圣灰星期三”
"It's late on Ash Wednesday."
我们能跳过那一步 罗伊
We can skip that part, Roy.
摘掉圣克里斯托弗项链
Take off the Saint Christopher's medal.
快
Now.
好吧
Okay.
很强大的阴气
Powerful stank.
黄金何在 死鬼？
Where's the gold, dead man?
检查这里的热水器
Check the water heater.
这里有超级警察在
Freaking super cop, here.
好吧 上马鞍
All right, saddle up.
我们要带你回去
We're gonna ride you in.
我知道这是错的
I know it's wrong,
可整个一个牛仔的说话方式
but the whole cowboy-talk thing,
这有点吸引我了
it's kind of working for me.
为什么你笑成那么样？
What do you got to smile about?
你喜欢和这个家伙共事吗？
Hey, how do you like working with this guy?
他是有点紧张 对不对？
He hangs on a little tight to stuff, huh?
我们在一起做什么与你无关
What we got together is none of your damn business.
剩余黄金在哪 海耶斯？
Where's the rest of the gold, Hayes?
明白我的意思了吗？他不会死心的
See what I mean? He won't let it die.
嘿 尼克 记得我中弹那事吗？
Hey, Nick, remember when I got shot?
我得奖了 而你不相信我会挺过去吗？
I got that medal, and you couldn't believe I pulled through?
瞎猜的 你没有挺过去吗？
Wild guess, you didn't pull through?
被一名吸毒者杀死 去了地狱
Get killed by some junkie and go to hell
就因为我贪污小钱为了看脱衣舞娘跳舞吗？
because I took a little on the side to pay for lap dances?
不 我认为不会
No. I don't think so.
谁去决定我命运？我接受不了
Who gets to make that call? I don't accept it.
嘿 让我问你
Hey, let me ask you something.
你认为永恒的惩罚是什么 海耶斯？
What do you think eternal punishment is gonna be like, Hayes?
可以亲我的屁股
Hell can kiss my ass.
我会留在这里
I'm staying right here.
“脱衣舞”
"Lap dancing."
看起来很漂亮
That's a nice look you got.
真漂亮 那脸蛋还有头发
That's nice, with the face and the hair.
来吧 坐下
All right, sit down.
你也许想要登记一下黄金
You might want to book that gold
在你的搭档出手之前
before your partner gets his hands on it.
这是什么？
What's this?
私人物品
That's personal.
那这个也得登记
Then it gets booked,
还有我带来的那堆黄金
along with this gold that I brought in.
听好了 娃娃脸
That's right, doll face.
别管我那胆小鬼似的停职令
Despite my chicken-shit suspension.
我或者可以提供提示
I'm available for a tutorial-type thing,
如果你或你们想要一些建议
if you or the guys want a few tips.
也许把你们提高到接近我的水准
Maybe get yourselves up near my level.
为什么我要爱你呢？
Why did I have to love you?
我们曾有过美丽的时刻
We had a beautiful moment in time.
一个灾难性的错误
Catastrophic mistake.
说清楚啊 可你感受到你要的东西
Run it down, but you felt what you felt.
坐下来
Take a seat.
好的 这可以让我
This is good, it's gonna help me
摆脱朝脸开枪的事
get over the shot-in-the-face thing.
无论在另一边等你的是什么
Whatever is waiting for you on the other side
那都是不“好”的
is gonna be bad.
不要担心 只是永远而已
Don't worry, it's only forever.
把这块黄金跟其余部分储藏起来
Stash this gold with the rest of it.
还有这个
And here.
嘿 我们刚刚登记了跟这一样的东西
Hey, we just booked something just like this.
是的 在那里的篮子里
It's in the basket over there.
你必须填写另外一份表格
You're gonna need to fill out another form.
非常乐意 我也没有其他好事可做
I'd love to. I've got nothing else better to do.
做腐尸还是有一件体面的事情 对吧？
There's one decent thing about being a Deado, right?
我们无法确切听到某些频率
We can't hear certain frequencies so well.
罗伊！
Roy!
来吧 尼克
Come on, Nicky.
你以为我会让你带我来这里吗
You thought I'd let you bring me here
要是我始终不想来这里的话？
if I didn't want to be here all along?
是不是很酷呢？
Isn't this thing sweet?
把你们都定住了 却对我们没影响
It freezes you guys up, does nothing to us.
他们得到了神器的所有一切
They got one of these artifacts for everything.
上 上 上！来吧！
Go, go, go! Come on!
拿走金子 带上所有东西！
Get the gold. Take everything!
全都在这儿吗？
It's all there?
接住！
Catch!
用所有手臂接住 来吧！
Fill up all these hands. Come on!
走了！走了！
Let's go! Let's go!
怎么了？
What's up?
安静
Peace.
冲洗
Flush it.
不！黄金！
No! The gold!
找你的 老板
Here, boss.
我都拿到了
I got it all.
我来了
I'm on it.
爸爸有黄金了！
Daddy's got gold!
动手兴建吧 孩子们！
Let's build it, boys!
该死的！卡住了
Damn it! It's jammed up.
这里就像是古代西部城市的主要街道
Just like Main Street, Dodge City.
这帮家伙
Them dudes,
他们选错了站立的地方
they picked the wrong venue to make a stand.
这东西就是我发明的
I invented this shit.
烫！
Hot!
修好了！真好！
I fixed it! Yeah!
上吧！
Go time!
教你一些古代西部射击的东西
Let's learn you a few things about Old West fighting.
第一
First,
只有菜鸟才藏在教堂塔尖上
only a novice hides in a church steeple.
这是我看的第一个地方
It's the first place I'm gonna look.
第二个地方 酒店的窗户 次次都中
Second place, hotel window, every time.
我估计在他的团队中只有一个菜鸟
I guess there's only one novice in their crew.
有时窗口的家伙是在屋顶上
Sometimes, the window guy is on the roof.
我从未看过这样的
I haven't seen that before.
这是监察员所说的大规模破坏
Must be the massive destruction Proctor was talking about.
上马鞍！
Saddle up!
嗨 朱莉娅
Hey, Julia.
海耶斯叫我们来接你
Hayes sent us to give you a lift.
大家好 我可以开车啊
Guys, I can still drive.
外面很乱
It's pretty hairy out there.
他只是担心你而已
He's just worried about you.
封锁这里
Close it up.
好的 封锁这里
All right. Lock it up.
没人可以通过联合大厦
Nobody gets through to the Commonwealth building.
没有！
Nobody!
看起来这个大家伙是在联合大厦附近
Looks like the big one is right over the Commonwealth building.
我们要去那里
That's where he'll be headed.
是的 我同意
Yeah. Good read.
你会同意我的看法？很奇怪啊
You're agreeing with me? That's weird.
是的 有点奇怪
Yeah. Feels strange.
还有点激动
Kind of tingly.
开车的腐尸
Deados on wheels.
令人失望
That's disappointing.
我还希望可以休息一阵
I was hoping to get a little break here.
让它走开 尼克！
Make it go away, Nick!
我明白
I got it.
我的天啊！
Holy shit!
刚才真的把我吓坏了
That actually scared the shit out of me.
黄金拿到顶上去
Get the gold up top.
我留下等最后那块
I gotta wait for the final piece.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
这到底是怎么回事？
What the hell is going on?
发生了很多情况 很高兴你能在这里
Lots going on. I'm glad you're here with me.
我们需要进去
We need to get inside.
听着 有件事我应该早说
Listen. There's something I should tell you.
我一直隐瞒着
It's something I've been hiding.
鲍比 可以等一等
Bobby, I think it can wait.
这可能有点怪
And it might seem a little weird.
但我想你应该保持开放的心态
But I think you should just try to keep an open mind,
不要马上评价 好吗？
and not judge right away, okay?
天空摄影4台正在现场连续直播
Skycam 4 is on the scene with continuing coverage.
我们在联合大楼上空往下看
We are looking down on the Commonwealth building
那里密集了…
which is swarming with,
我不知怎么说只能形容为
there's really no other way to say this,
怪物
monsters.
我呼吁大家留在室内 直至情况…
I urge everyone to stay inside until this situation...
戴夫！
Dave!
好险
Wicked.
看起来他们制造了一个路障
Looks like they built a barricade.
又是那肥猫王
And there's Fat Elvis.
撞死这肥胖子
Hit him in the jiggly.
不错！
Not bad!
放开我的车门！
My door!
摆脱不了我的！
Can't shake me!
仍在这里！
Still here, dicks!
放松身体
Relax body.
死去吧
Death.
我希望他们能有电梯
I hope they have an elevator.
该死的
Shit.
扭转死亡隧道 死人将回落下来
Reverse the tunnel, the dead come pouring back.
我们将永远地留在这里
We stay here forever.
现在是击掌的时候了
Kind of a high-five moment.
我们所要做的就是激活这坏小子
All we gotta do is fire up this bad boy.
好！
Yeah!
好的
Okay.
这可能会令人有一点点不舒服
This is where it gets a little uncomfortable.
因为没法好好形容 我只能直说
There's no great way to say this, so I'll just say it.
这种古老仪式 往往包含了一种要素
These ancient things, they often involve an element of,
我不想说的就是“人祭”
I don't want to say "human sacrifice,"
但就是人祭
but human sacrifice.
你碰到我之前 我会跳下去
I'll jump before you can even touch me.
朱莉娅 拜托 冷静点
Julia, come on. Be cool.
这是种荣耀
This is an honor.
我信任你才选择你担负重任
I'm trusting you with the heavy shit.
朱莉娅！
Julia!
时间刚刚好
Just in time.
鲍比！不要！
Bobby! Don't!
不！
No!
闪开！
Move!
射的好
Nice shot.
我要去救朱莉娅 你处理那东西
I'm gonna go get Julia. You take care of the Staff.
那黄金东西会倒塌的
That golden pecker is coming down.
你准备好了吗？
You frosty?
冰火 搭档
Icy hot, partner.
现在怎么样 尼克？
What now, Nick?
你知道的 不一定是朱莉娅的
You know, it didn't have to be Julia,
但是我总想把事情弄的圆满些
but I just couldn't resist bringing it full circle.
来吧 很不错 对吧？
Come on. It's good, right?
给我过来！
Get over here!
你怎么样了 罗伊？
How's it coming, Roy?
这比想像的更难处理！
It's harder than it looks!
杀你这件事我总玩不厌 尼克
Killing you never gets old, Nicky.
随时都行啊！
Any time now!
我听到了！
I hear you!
来吧 罗伊！
Come on, Roy!
做些牛仔会做的事情！
Do some cowboy stuff!
拜托！
Please!
罗伊！
Roy!
这就对了！
There it is.
不
No.
那么 好搭档
Well, partner.
我有一个新搭档了
I have a new partner.
我很想念你
I missed you.
我太想念你了
I missed you so much.
抱歉 非常抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
没关系 现在你和我在一起了
It's okay, you're back with me now.
这就是我想要的一切
That's all I wanted.
但并非以这样的方式
But not like this.
朱莉娅 你要好好生活下去
Julia, you gotta live your life,
即使没有我
without me.
我不想说再见
I don't want to say goodbye.
你不能呆在这里
You can't stay here.
没关系
It's okay.
去吧
Go.
我永远爱你
I will always love you.
再见
Goodbye.
她会没事的
She's gonna be okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这回你欠我了
You owe me for that.
我们来算帐吧
Let's settle up.
当然
Sure.
我希望允许我设计我自己的奖牌
I would like to be allowed to design my own medal.
没有这么快
Not so fast.
永恒部门在你们没出席的情况下继续进行了纪律审判
The Eternals went ahead and had your disciplinary hearing without you.
在我们拯救世界的时候？
While we were saving the world?
尼克 作为新警员 仅一次警告
Nick, as a new recruit, you've been let off with a warning.
还算合理
Reasonable.
- 罗伊 有惩罚…   - 惩罚？
- Roy, as punishment... - "Punishment"?
是的 你的任期再增加53年
Yes. Fifty-three more years have been added to your term.
53年？
Fifty-three years?
那太多了
That's a lot.
这全是扯淡
This is honky-tonk bullshit.
你就是喜欢把我留在身旁 是吧 米尔德丽德？
You just like having me around, don't you, Mildred?
我的帽子
My hat.
你帮我找到了它？
You went off and found it?
我想我可以时不时再买一些花送你
I guess I could've bought you flowers once or twice.
我喜欢紫罗兰(暴力)
I like violets.
她咬了我的胡子
She "billy goat-ed" me.
这是我们以前常做的事情
It's something we used to do.
她刻意用白色的靴子把脚踝包起来
Why she covers up them ankles with them damn white boots
我永远无法理解
I'll never understand.
你还有53年 不是吗？
Fifty-three more years, huh?
不 我还有一些工作要做
Well, I still got some things to work on.
我这已是第三次延长了
Hell, this is the third time I've been extended.
对了 我给你带了点东西
Say, I got you something.
是什么？
What's this?
我知道你不喜欢陈大爷的外表
I knew you weren't happy with Grandpa Chen,
所以我走了点关系 给你一个新的身份外表
so I pulled a few strings, got you some new ID.
我很感激  谢谢你 罗伊 我是认真的
Thank you. Thank you, Roy. I mean that.
那太捧了
This is great.
你是在跟我开玩笑吧
You gotta be shitting me.
我做了我所能做的  毕竟资源有限啊
I did what I could. Inventory is what it is.
你认为这算是一种进步吗？
You thought this was an improvement?